healthblurbs.com 2010-03-27

# HealthBlurbs.com Privacy Policy » Health Blurbs

At healthblurbs.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit healthblurbs.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Personally Identifiable Information**

“Personally identifiable information” is any information that can identify or locate a particular person, including but not limited to name, address, telephone number, email address, social security number, bank account number or credit card number.  Healthblurbs.com does not collect this type of information.

In general, you can visit healthblurbs.com without telling us who you are or providing any information about yourself.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL orShaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.

**Third Party Advertisers**

We use Google’s Adsense and other third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the policies or practices of these third-party advertisers.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We have contracted with ValueClick to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement ‘click-throughs’, and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, ValueClick and its business partners may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by ValueClick, please see ValueClick’s privacy policy at<http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml>.

Healthblurbs.com reserves the right to change the terms, conditions, and notices in this privacy policy.
